# question_data = [
# {"text": "A slug's blood is green.", "answer": "True"},
# {"text": "The loudest animal is the African Elephant.", "answer": "False"},
# {"text": "Approximately one quarter of human bones are in the feet.", "answer": "True"},
# {"text": "The total surface area of a human lungs is the size of a football pitch.", "answer": "True"},
# {"text": "In West Virginia, USA, if you accidentally hit an animal with your car, you are free to take it home to eat.", "answer": "True"},
# {"text": "In London, UK, if you happen to die in the House of Parliament, you are entitled to a state funeral.", "answer": "False"},
# {"text": "It is illegal to pee in the Ocean in Portugal.", "answer": "True"},
# {"text": "You can lead a cow down stairs but not up stairs.", "answer": "False"},
# {"text": "Google was originally called 'Backrub'.", "answer": "True"},
# {"text": "Buzz Aldrin's mother's maiden name was 'Moon'.", "answer": "True"},
# {"text": "No piece of square dry paper can be folded in half more than 7 times.", "answer": "False"},
# {"text": "A few ounces of chocolate can to kill a small dog.", "answer": "True"}
# ]

question_data = [
        {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Science: Mathematics","question":"The &#039;Squaring the Circle&#039; problem is solvable.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Science: Mathematics","question":"The set of all algebraic numbers is countable.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Science: Mathematics","question":"Zero factorial is equal to zero. ","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science: Mathematics","question":"If you could fold a piece of paper in half 50 times, its&#039; thickness will be 3\/4th the distance from the Earth to the Sun.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Science: Mathematics","question":"An equilateral triangle always has every angle measuring 60&deg;.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science: Mathematics","question":"L&#039;H&ocirc;pital was the mathematician who created the homonymous rule that uses derivatives to evaluate limits with indeterminations.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Science: Mathematics","question":"E = MC3","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science: Mathematics","question":"The binary number &quot;101001101&quot; is equivalent to the Decimal number &quot;334&quot;","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Science: Mathematics","question":"An isosceles triangle has two sides of equal length as opposed to three.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Science: Mathematics","question":"111,111,111 x 111,111,111 = 12,345,678,987,654,321","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]}
        ]